http://www.thewaldorfschool.org/privacy-policy

Endowment
Privacy Policy of www.thewaldorfschool.orgThis application (hereinafter “Application”) collects some Personal Data from its Users.The Data are collected and processed for the purposes set out below.DATA PROCESSING OWNERSHIPWaldorf School of Lexington 739 Massachusetts Ave Lexington, Massachusetts 02420info@thewaldorfschool.org TYPES OF DATA COLLECTEDAmong the Data that this Application may collect there are: Cookie and Browsing and usage Data. Other Personal Data collected may be highlighted by other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text, in the moment when the Data collection happens. The Personal Data may be freely inserted by the User or the Data Subject, or collected automatically when using the Application. Any use of Cookies by the Application or the owners of third party services used by the Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify the User and remember his/her preferences for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User. Failure to provide certain Personal Data, in particular Navigation Data, by deactivating the Application’s Cookies may make it impossible to surf or for the Application to provide its services. The Personal Data collected may regard both the User and third parties whose data the User provides. The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through the Application and declares that they have the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the Owner of all responsibility towards third parties.MODE AND PLACE OF PROCESSING THE DATA OBTAINEDMethod of ProcessingThe Data Controller processes the Data of the Interested Parties and Users in a lawful and proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Data. Processing is carried out using computers and / or telematic means, with organizational methods and logics strictly related to the stated purposes.In addition to the owner, in some cases, access to the Data may be available to external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies). The updated list of Managers may be requested from the Owner at any time.PlaceThe Data are processed at the headquarters of the Data Controller, unless stated otherwise in the rest of this document.Conservation TimeThe Data are kept for the time necessary to perform the service requested by the User, and the User can always ask for their suspension or removal.THE USE OF THE COLLECTED DATAThe Data concerning the User or the Data Subject are collected for the following purposes: Advertising and Analytics.The kinds of Personal Data used for each purpose are given in the specific sections of this policy.The use of Data for additional purposes by the Owner may in some cases, and for legal purposes, require specific consent by the User or the Data Subject. THIRD PARTY LINKSThe Application may contain links and references to non-application websites and resources (“Linked Websites”) and are provided for convenience only. We will have no liability arising out of or related to such Linked Websites and/or their content or any damages or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection of any purchase or use of any such content, goods or services available on or through any such Linked Website. We are not responsible for the content, accuracy or opinions expressed on these websites. Inclusion of these links on our application does not apply approval or endorsement by of the Linked Websites, their entities or products and services. The application is not a party to or responsible for any transaction you may enter into with any such third party, even if you learn of such third party from the application, by way of reference or link provided on the application.DETAILED INFORMATION ON THE PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA AND THE SERVICES PROVIDED BY THIRD PARTIESPersonal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:AdvertisingAnalytics ADDITIONAL INFORMATION ABOUT DATA PROCESSINGLegal ProtectionThe User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner of the Application in court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from its improper use or that of related services by the User.Additional InformationSpecific information may be shown on the pages of the Site concerning particular services or the processing of Data provided by the User or by the Data Subject.MaintenanceThe User’s Personal Data may be further used in ways and for purposes required for Application maintenance.System LogsFor operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services it uses may collect system logs, i.e., files that record interaction – including navigation.They may also contain personal data, such as IP addresses.Information not contained in this policyMore information on processing Personal Information may be requested from the Owner at any time.The Rights of Data SubjectsThose persons to whom the Data refer have the right, at any time, to know whether their data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Owner of the Processing System.Changes to this Privacy PolicyThe Application reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page, and by ensuring analogous protection of the Personal Information in all cases. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom.DEFINITIONS AND LEGAL REFERENCESPersonal information or DataAny information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.Browsing and usage DataInformation collected automatically from the Site, including the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the users who connect to the site, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the visitor, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page) and the details about the path followed within the site with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the operating system and the user's IT environment.UserMeans the individual user of the Application’s services or productsData SubjectThe legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data referData ProcessorThe natural person, legal person, public administration or any other organization, association or organization designated by the Data Controller for the Personal Data processing system. Data ControllerThe natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Site.Legal informationNotice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies.This privacy policy exclusively regards this Application.
